Marcel Breuer Papers
Marcel Breuer Papers
- Project Records, 1922-1982 (inclusive); 1940-1980 (bulk); 89 linear feet of manuscript material, 24,618 drawings, 6,160 photographs and slides.
  - SAINT JOHN'S LIBRARY, Collegeville, MN (1964-1966) [Religious]
    - Drawings, 282
      - Presentation Set: Schematic Floor Plans, Programming, Site Plan (17 Jun 1960): Cover sheet, Sheet Nos. 1-4, multiple version of Sheet No. 2, [Presentation Drawings]; 6; (originals) (Tube 1467)
      - Presentation Set (30 Aug 1960) (Sheet Nos. 1-4): Main Floor, Lower Floor, Partial Cross Section, Lower Floor, [Presentation Drawings]; 4; (originals) (Tube 1467)
      - Presentation Sheet (n.d.): Section showing tree column, [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1467)
      - Presentation Set (n.d.): Sheet nos. 1-7, [Presentation Drawings]; 7; (reproductions) (Tube 1467)
      - Presentation Set: Library Building (Oct 1964): Title Sheet/Reflected Ceiling Plan, Site Plan (Dwg. No. 1), Upper Floor (Dwg. No. 2), Lower Floor Plan (Dwg. No. 3), Mezzanine Floor Plan and Construction Plan (Dwg. No. 4), Elevations and Sections (Dwg. Nos. 5-6), [Presentation Drawings]; 7; (originals) (Tube 1467)
    - Project Files
      - Bid Documents (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Change Orders (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Contracts, Owner-Architect Agreement (1960), Owner-Contractor Agreement (1964) (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Associated Architects (1964), Hanson-Michelson, Architects (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Awards (1968), AIA Library Building Awards Program (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Client (1959-61), St. John's University (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence: Client (1963), St. John's University (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence: Client (Jan-May 1964), St. John's University (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence: Client (Jun-Dec 1964), St. John's University (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence: Client (1965-68), St. John's University (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1960-66), Gausman Moore, Cons. Engineers (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1960-66), Johnston-Sahlman Co., Cons. Engineers (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1964), Miscellaneous Consultants (Box 101, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1964-66), Cold Spring Electric Co. (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1964-66), Gunnar I. Johnson Son, Inc. (Box 101, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence: Donors (1964), Dr. James Kritzeck (Box 101, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence: Field Office (1965-66), David Vachon (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence: Grant (1965-66), Title 45 Grant Materials: Housing Home Finance Agency; Dept. of Health, Education Welfare (Box 101, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1960-65), Cold Spring Granite Co. (Box 101, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1963), Contract Interiors, Inc. (Library Reading Table) (Box 101, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1964), Century Lighting (Box 101, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1960-66), Various Suppliers and Service Providers (Box 101, Folder 22)
      - Financial Records I (1957-1968), Architectural Invoices (Box 101, Folder 23)
      - Financial Records II, Certificates of Payment (Box 101, Folder 24)
      - Financial Records III, Consultant Invoices (Box 101, Folder 25)
      - Financial Records IV, Housing and Home Finance Agency Periodic Estimates for Partial Payment (Box 101, Folder 26)
      - Office Records I, St. John's University Building Committee Meeting Minutes (Box 102, Folder 27)
      - Office Records II, Interoffice Memoranda (Box 102, Folder 28)
      - Office Records III, Miscellaneous Notes (Box 102, Folder 29)
      - Office Records IV, Project Records (Box 102, Folder 30)
      - Product Literature (Box 102, Folder 31)
      - Program (Box 102, Folder 32)
      - Specifications, Specifications for Furnishings and Equipment (Box 102, Folder 33)
      - Testing Reports, Twin City Testing and Engineering Laboratory; Soil Exploration Co. (Box 102, Folder 34)
      - Transmittals (Box 102, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence: Client: Library Ecumenical Offices. (1967), St. John's University (Box 102, Folder 1B)
      - Correspondence: Consultants: Library Ecumenical Offices (1967), Gausman Moore, Consulting Engineers (Box 102, Folder 2B)
      - Correspondence: Contractor: Library Ecumenical Offices (1967), M.A. Mortenson Co., Gen. Contractor (Box 102, Folder 3B)
      - Financials I: Library Ecumenical Offices (1957-1968), Architectural Invoices (Box 102, Folder 4B)
      - Financials II: Library Ecumenical Offices, Consultant Invoices- Gausman Moore, Consulting Engineers (Box 102, Folder 5B)
      - Transmittals: Library Ecumenical Offices (Box 102, Folder 6B)
    - Published Material
      - A Pictorial Review of the New Library The Off-Campus Record St. John's University (Winter 1965), pgs. 16; (Magazine) (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - Photographs, 30
      - Progress Photos of Reading Room and Stacks, construction, interior view; (black and white photographs) 7 (Box 102, Folder 37)
      - Progress Photos of Façade Construction, construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 19 (Box 102, Folder 37)
      - Close-Up of "Tree Column" in Main Reading Room, finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 102, Folder 38)
      - Exterior Wall Detail, finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 102, Folder 38)
      - Elevation View from the North, finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 102, Folder 38)
  - SAINT JOHN'S MONASTERY WING, Collegeville, MN (1954-1955) [Religious], (Alternate names: St. John's Monastery)
    - Drawings, 245
      - Detail Rendering: Brothers' Recreation Room Fireplace. [pen and ink, applied film and opaque white on illustration board, 15 x 20 in.], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 15)
      - Detail Rendering: Fathers' Recreation Room Fireplace. [pen and ink, applied film and opaque white on illustration board, 15 x 20 in.], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 15)
      - Project Sketches of Monastery Gardens, [Design Development Drawings]; 2; (originals) (Box 91)
      - Prelim. Plan of Monastery Gardens, [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Box 91)
      - SK Drawings: 70, 71 (3), 72, 75, 77, 81, 84, 95B, 1 Unlabeled, [Working Drawings]; 11; (originals) (Box 91)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A-4 to A-18 incomplete), [Working Drawings]; 12; (reproductions) (Tube 253)
      - Third Floor Heating and Ventilating Plan, [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 253)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A-2, A-3, A-4, A-5, A-6, A-16): Door Location Plans and Schedules, [Working Drawings]; 6; (reproductions) (Tube 254)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Mechanical (Dwg. Nos. M0-M4), [Working Drawings]; 5; (reproductions) (Tube 254)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Plumbing (Dwg. Nos. P-2, P-3, P-4, P-5), [Working Drawings]; 4; (reproductions) (Tube 254)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954- 20 Sep 1954): Electrical (Dwg. Nos. E1-E4), [Working Drawings]; 4; (reproductions) (Tube 254)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Plumbing ( P6): Stair No. 5 Sprinkler System, [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 254)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Structural (Dwg. Nos. S1-S9), [Working Drawings]; 9; (reproductions) (Tube 254)
      - H-1 to H-8 (Bound in Set): Heating and Ventilating Plans and Details, [Working Drawings]; 8; (reproductions) (Tube 254)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A1-A25), [Working Drawings]; 25; (reproductions) (Tube 255)
      - SK Drawings 1-94 (Discontinuous): Details and Alternate Layout Schemes, [Working Drawings]; 72; (originals) (Tube 701)
      - Sketch Survey of Existing Building with Colored Differentiation of Elevation Zones, [Site Surveys]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1123)
      - Counter Proposal for Monastery Wing with Multiple Variations, [Design Development Drawings]; 3; (reproductions) (Tube 1123)
      - Various Unnumbered Sketches for Details dated Aug. 1953- Feb. 1955; Door Schedule, [Working Drawings]; 20; (originals) (Tube 1123)
      - SK-4, SK-90: Prelim. Wall Sections and Photo-Mural Mounting Panels, [Working Drawings]; 2; (originals) (Tube 1123)
      - F-1, F-2, F-6: Furniture Layouts for Various Monastery Wing Rooms; Bench Design, [Working Drawings]; 3; (mixed) (Tube 1123)
      - Construction Set: Landscaping (L-1, L-2), [Working Drawings]; 2; (originals) (Tube 1123)
      - Presentation Set (Sheet nos.1-3): Floor Plans at Three Levels, [Presentation Drawings]; 3; (originals) (Tube 1135)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A1-A25), [Working Drawings]; 25; (originals) (Tube 1135)
      - 15-21 February 1956: Sheets C1-C3 and F7: Furniture and Cabinetry for Abbot's Chapel, [Working Drawings]; 4; (originals) (Tube 1135)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954- 20 Sep 1954): Electrical (Dwg. Nos. E1-E4), [Working Drawings]; 4; (originals) (Tube 1136)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Structural (Dwg. Nos. S1-S9), [Working Drawings]; 9; (originals) (Tube 1136)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Plumbing ( P6): Stair No. 5 Sprinkler System, [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1136)
      - Construction Set (28 May 1954): Mechanical (Dwg. Nos. SMO, M1-M4), [Working Drawings]; 5; (originals) (Tube 1136)
      - Correspondence: Associated Architects (1954-56), Traynor Hermanson, Architects (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Client (1953), St. John's Abbey: Fr. Meinberg, Fr. Eidenschink, Rt. Rev. Dworschak (Abbot), Karmarcik (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Client (1954), St. John's Abbey: Fr. Meinberg, Fr. Eidenschink, Rt. Rev. Dworschak (Abbot), Karmarcik (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Client (1955), St. John's Abbey: Fr. Meinberg, Fr. Eidenschink, Rt. Rev. Dworschak (Abbot), Karmarcik (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Client (1956-57), St. John's Abbey: Fr. Meinberg, Fr. Eidenschink, Rt. Rev. Dworschak (Abbot), Karmarcik (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence: Consultant (1955), Josef Albers (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence: Consultant (1954), Cowin Co., Inc. (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence: Consultant (1954), Farkas Barron, Cons. Structural Engineers (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Financial Records I, Architectural Invoices (Box 91, Folder 19)
      - Financial Records II, Certificates of Payment- Farkas Barron, Cons. Structural Engineers (Box 91, Folder 20)
      - Financial Records III, Certificates of Payment- Fred S. Dubin Assoc., Cons. Mechanical Engineers (Box 91, Folder 21)
      - Financial Records IV, Certificates of Payment- Wahl Construction Co., Gen. Contractors (Box 91, Folder 22)
      - Financial Records V, Certificates of Payment- Yager Plumbing Heating, Contractors (Box 91, Folder 23)
      - Negatives for Photomurals (Box 91, Folder 24)
      - Office Records I, Project Memoranda (Box 91, Folder 25)
      - Office Records II, Scale Model (Box 91, Folder 26)
      - Office Records III, Travel Documents (Box 91, Folder 27)
      - Program (Box 91, Folder 28)
      - Specifications, General Specifications (Box 91, Folder 29)
      - Transmittals I, Covin Co., Inc. (Box 91, Folder 30)
      - Transmittals II, Farkas Barron, Structural Engineers (Box 91, Folder 31)
      - Transmittals III, Fred S. Dubin Assoc., Cons. Mechanical Engineers (Box 91, Folder 32)
      - Transmittals IV, Various Suppliers and Service Providers (Box 91, Folder 33)
      - Transmittals V, Various Suppliers and Service Providers (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - Photographs, 12
      - Brothers' Recreation Room, finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 91, Folder 37)
      - [Slide 9], drawings, plan; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - [Slide 10], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - End Wall [Slide 47], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - [Slide 147], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - View At a Distance with Site Context [Slide 151], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Group of Monks with Monastery Building in Background [Slide 155], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - [Slide 156], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Partial Elevation [Slide 602], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Monastic Cell [Slide 636], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Abbot's Office [Slide 640], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Sacristy? [Slide 641], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-6)
  - SAINT JOHN'S RESIDENCE HALL I, Collegeville, MN (1957-1959) [Religious]
    - Drawings, 115
      - Construction Set [4 Feb 1958]: Mechanical (M1-M9); Electrical (E1-E4), [Working Drawings]; 13; (reproductions) (Tube 261)
      - Construction Set [4 Feb 1958] (annotated prints, some with sketches on back of sheets): Architectural (Title sheet, A2-A5, A7-A19); Structural (S1-S6); Mechanical (M1-M9); Electrical (E1-E4), [Working Drawings]; 37; (reproductions) (Tube 262)
      - SK Drawings [Feb 1958-Mar 1961] (annotated prints): Architectural (SKA2-SKA4, SKA6-SKA9); Structural (SKS1-SKS3); Mechanical (SKM1-SKM2); Electrical (SKEM-3RJ); SKLU1, [Working Drawings]; 14; (reproductions) (Tube 262)
      - Construction Set [4 Feb 1958]: Architectural (A1-A19); Structural (S1-S6), [Working Drawings]; 25; (originals) (Tube 1337)
      - SK Drawings and Misc. Details [Feb-Oct 1958]: SK1, SKA1-SKA12 (incomplete), SKS1-SKS3, Painting 1-2, Special Issue (P1), SKM1 and unnumbered, [Working Drawings]; 19; (originals) (Tube 1338)
      - Furniture [Mar 1958-Mar 1959]: F1A, F2, F2A, F3A, F3a, F3b, [Working Drawings]; 7; (originals) (Tube 1338)
    - Project Files
      - Bid Documents: Furnishings (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Change Orders (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Assoc. Architects (1957-58), Traynor Hermanson, Architects (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Client (1957-58), St. John's University (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Client (1959-[1963]), St. John's University (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1957-60), Gausman Moore, Cons. Engineers (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1957-58, [1963]), Wiesenfeld, Hayward Leon, Cons. Engineers (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1958-59), Maurice Mandel, Inc. (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence: Financing (1958-59), Housing Home Finance Agency (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1958-61), Various Suppliers and Service Providers (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence: Publicity (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence: Regulatory Agencies (1957-60), Minnesota State Fire Marshal, Dept. of Health, Industrial Commission of Minnesota (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Financial Records I, Architectural Invoices (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Financial Records II, Consultant Invoices (Box 93, Folder 14)
      - Financial Records III, Periodic Estimates and Construction Reports (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Financial Records IV, Insurance Documents (Box 93, Folder 16)
      - Office Records I, Housing and Home Finance Agency Office File (Box 93, Folder 17)
      - Office Records II (1958-1959), Internal Correspondence With Field Office: Val Michelson (Box 93, Folder 18)
      - Office Records III, Project Memoranda (Box 93, Folder 19)
      - Office Records IV, Travel Documents (Box 93, Folder 20)
      - Specifications I, Furnishings Proposals (Box 93, Folder 21)
      - Specifications II, Furniture Schedules (Box 93, Folder 22)
      - Specifications III, Specifications for Transformer Installation (Box 93, Folder 23)
      - Testing Reports I, Foundation Investigation (Box 93, Folder 24)
      - Testing Reports II, Twin City Testing Laboratory (Concrete Compression Tests, Cement Reports) (Box 93, Folder 25)
      - Transmittals, Various Suppliers and Service Providers (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Published Material
      - Johnnies Enjoy Plush Quarters (25 Sept 1959), 1; (newspaper clippings) (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - About 500 Persons Attended the Dedication… The Record (Official newspaper of St. John's) (August 1959), 1; (newspaper clippings) (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - Brothers Fashion New Desks The Record (Official newspaper of St. John's) (27 Feb 1959), 1; (newspaper clippings) (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - Aquin Hall to Dedicated Aug. 9 The Record (Official newspaper of St. John's) (24 July 1959), 1; (newspaper clippings) (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - Thomas Hall at Night [Photograph and Caption] The Record (Official newspaper of St. John's) (23 Oct 1959), 1; (newspaper clippings) (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - New Church, St. Thomas Hall Ahead of Schedule The Record (Official newspaper of St. John's) (10 Oct 1958), 1; (newspaper clippings) (Box 93, Folder 63)
    - Photographs, 30
      - Negatives of Images for Photomural, art work, detail; (negatives) 10 (Box 93, Folder 27)
      - 3 x 5 Photos with Negatives of "Block Damage", finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 14 (Box 93, Folder 27)
      - 8 x 10 Photographs of "Block Damage", finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 5 (Box 93, Folder 27)
      - View of Two Elevations (Mounted on Board), finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - SAINT JOHN'S RESIDENCE HALL II, Collegeville, MN (1965-1967) [Religious]
    - Drawings, 123
      - SK A-4: Detail for Etched Emblems in Glass Panels, [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Box 106)
      - F-2 through F-8A: Furniture Layouts for Various Rooms; Details for a Bookcase, [Working Drawings]; 10; (mixed) (Box 106)
      - Perspective Rendering (Artist Unknown, n.d.) [graphite on illustration board, 12 x 28 in], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 115, Folder 3)
      - Construction Set [15 Feb 1966] ("bid set") (annotated prints): Architectural (A0-A20); Electrical (E1-E9, A9); Mechanical (M1-M11, A9), [Working Drawings]; 42; (reproductions) (Tube 259)
      - Construction Set [15 Feb 1966] ("revised bid set") (annotated prints): Architectural (A0-A20); Structural (S1-S7); Electrical (E1-E9); Mechanical (M1-M11), [Working Drawings]; 47; (reproductions) (Tube 260)
      - Construction Set [15 Feb 1966]: Architectural (A0-A21), [Working Drawings]; 22; (originals) (Tube 1356)
    - Project Files
      - Bid Documents (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Change Orders (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Client (1961-64), St. John's University (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Client (1965-68), St. John's University (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1966-67), Various Consultants (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1965-67), Edward Zekala, Architectural Specifications (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1965-68), Gausman Moore, Consulting Engineers (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1965-68), Johnston-Sahlman Co., Consulting Engineers (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1966-68), M.A. Mortenson Co., Gen. Contractor (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1966-67), Knapp Plumbing Heating, Inc. (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1966), Cold Spring Electric Co. (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence: Field Office (1966-67), Norman Dorf, David Vachon, Noel Jones (Field Engineer) (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence: Grant (1966), Dept. of Housing Urban Development Application Materials, HHFA Periodic Inspection Reports (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1966-67), Various Suppliers and Service Providers (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1965-66), Cold Spring Granite Co. (Box 105, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence: Regulatory Agencies (1966), Minnesota Fire Marshall (Box 105, Folder 16)
      - Financial Records I (1957-1968), Architectural Invoices (Box 106, Folder 17)
      - Financial Records II, Building Costs (Box 106, Folder 18)
      - Financial Records III, Certificates of Payment- Cold Spring Electric Co. (Box 106, Folder 19)
      - Financial Records IV, Certificates of Payment- Knapp Plumbing Heating (Box 106, Folder 20)
      - Financial Records V, Certificates of Payment- M.A. Mortenson Co. (Box 106, Folder 21)
      - Financial Records VI, Consultant Invoices (Box 106, Folder 22)
      - Financial Records VII, Insurance Certificate (Box 106, Folder 23)
      - Office Records I, Field Office Expenses (Box 106, Folder 24)
      - Office Records II, Memoranda (Box 106, Folder 25)
      - Program, Program/Area Break-Down (Box 106, Folder 26)
      - Punch Lists (Box 106, Folder 27)
      - Site Certificate, Includes Site Survey (Box 106, Folder 28)
      - Specifications, Prelim. Specification for Mechanical Utilities Work, Furnishing Specifications (Box 106, Folder 29)
      - Testing Reports, Soil Exploration Co. (Box 106, Folder 30)
      - Transmittals I, Transmittals to Bidders for Contract (Box 106, Folder 31)
      - Transmittals II (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - Photographs, 18
      - 3 1/2 x 5 inch Progress Photos of Façade Construction, construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 5 (Box 106, Folder 33)
      - Stair Railing Installation, construction, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 106, Folder 33)
      - Façade Construction Progress, construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 9 (Box 106, Folder 33)
      - Views of Facades and Close-Ups, finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 3 (Box 106, Folder 34)
  - SAINT JOHN'S SCIENCE BUILDING, Collegeville, MN (1964-1966) [Religious]
    - Drawings, 375
      - Construction Set (1 Mar 1965) (annotated prints): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A0-A27), [Working Drawings]; 28; (reproductions) (Tube 257)
      - Construction Set (1 Mar 1965) (prints of revised sheets): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A24-A27), [Working Drawings]; 4; (reproductions) (Tube 257)
      - Occupancy and Egress Set (13 Nov 1964), [Working Drawings]; 5; (reproductions) (Tube 257)
      - Construction Set [1 Mar 1965]: Architectural (A0-A21, A23-A27), [Working Drawings]; 27; (originals) (Tube 1334)
      - Test Boring and Survey Data (6 Jul 1964), [Site Surveys]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1334)
      - SK Drawing Set (Sep 1964-Jan 1965): SK1-SK100, incomplete, [Design Development Drawings]; 40; (originals) (Tube 1335)
      - SK-D (13 Jan 1964), [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1335)
      - SK-B-1 (n.d.), [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1335)
      - SK Architectural Set (Aug 1965-Oct 1965): SK-A-1 to SK-A-19 and unnumbered, [Design Development Drawings]; 28; (originals) (Tube 1335)
      - Architect's Report [Aug 1964] [1 set negative photostats, 1 set positive photostats]: Sheets 1-9, [Presentation Drawings]; 18; (reproductions) (Tube 1336)
      - Presentation Set [Aug 1964] [1 complete set and 2 duplicate sets w/o Sheet No. 8]: Site Plan, Floor Plans, Elevations, Sections, Auditorium Sections (Sheet Nos. 1-8), [Presentation Drawings]; 22; (mixed) (Tube 1336)